[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Fed"]}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "WP", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 23, "question": "What do you make of it all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 24, "answer": "Well, it was really, the financial markets were having a hard time figuring out exactly what the Fed said in a really unprecedented statement.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBP", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "``", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "''", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "Where do you think we actually are?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Well, the thing is that for those who have been saying, you know, be calm, carry on -- through all of this -- you know, feel a little bit of \"I told you so\" today.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "CC", "VB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "And until job numbers improve, the American people are not going to feel better and feel confident in this economy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "CC", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "I want to put all three of you on the spot here and ask you: where should the average American put their money now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "Where should an American put their money right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "Well, I'm not an advisor, an investment advisor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "You've used way past your limit but what kind of stocks quickly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "I'm still very bullish on exports and multinationals, manufacturers and that sector.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "Leigh Gallagher, can we try the 10-word rule with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "I'll try.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Leigh Gallagher"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "Where are you going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "Was that 11?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "I think you actually did that in under 10 words.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "What did you make of a Fed statement today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Well, I think it was appropriate.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Fed"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "U.S."]}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "RBR", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "Why do you believe that they may be a friend?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "I think -- I was talking about the immediate crisis, the financial crisis going on now despite all of the bombasts coming from the Chinese side about how America needs to pull up the socks and behave better and similar bombasts in the U.S. side, fundamentally, their interests are the same as ours at the moment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "How do you imagine that conversation went?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "I would imagine it would be a little different from the public discourse.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "``", "VBN", "TO", "WP", "''", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "Is it healthy or unhealthy that China holds so much of the American debt right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "It's a \"compared to what\" question.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "WDT", "VBP", "RBR", "CC", "JJR", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "Is it time for America Incorporated to revisit this whole area, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "Well, there are aspects of China's performance which are more and less impressive when you're there.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["London"]}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "Dan, what's the latest from London tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "Well, the police are all over this area of east London, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["IPCC"]}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "What is your understanding of where are in that investigation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "Well, we still haven't gotten a complete picture of the IPCC.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 290, "question": "Is there a social malaise that has created an underclass of kids who feel they got no education, no hope of getting a job, and this is the tinderbox, if you like, being lit to a deeper problem?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "Yes, I think that's fair.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "How bad is it, do you think, right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Well, clearly the news is grim on a lot of fronts, the economy being first and foremost.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "Do you see any sign of what it could be, which will rejuvenate America and Americans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "CC", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "Well, if I were going to dub this era something, I would call it generation downsize.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "How do you get Americans back to work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNPS", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "I think you're going to have to put a jobs plan, and fight Congress on it, in which we deal with what some people would call the Smart Grid or a green grid.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "JJS", ",", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "What are Obama's chances right now, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "I would say his chances right now are 50-50 at best, maybe trending that line down.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Doug Brinkley, do you agree, 50/50 at best for the president to be reelected?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "CD", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "I think 50/50.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Doug Brinkley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RBR", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ":", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Do you think America ten years on is in a better or worse place?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "I think we're better of in this regard, Piers -- and sometimes I can't imagine it's been ten years, because I think about it almost every day.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "But certainly needs a little bit of J.R. action doesn't it, right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "We need action, no question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1951"]}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "Do you feel slightly compromised when you stand up for something that would help your business like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "When you say I'm in the business -- of course, I'm a geologist and I've been in the business since I got out of school in 1951.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["four trillion dollars"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Congress", "S&P"]}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "RP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "CD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "How should President Obama get this great country back being great again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "Well, I was disappointed in Congress when they struggled to make a decision and finally came up -- they had been told by S&P that four trillion -- it was going to take a four trillion dollars cut in spending.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "Where do you sit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "Well, I think they're a competitor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110809pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "Finally, who do you have in your eye to be the Republican candidate that may take on President Obama in the election next year?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}]